in this video I'll be demonstrating some
在这段视频中，我将演示一些
of the more advanced Transformations
更高级的转型
that you can make when working with
您可以在使用时
nodes and inkscape by showing you how to
节点和Inkscape，向您展示如何
create this cassette tape design and
创建这个盒式磁带设计和
this will be more of an advanced
这将是一种更高级的
tutorial in that I'm not going to be
关于我不会成为
going over every step in fine detail but
每一步都细致入微，但是
if you're already somewhat familiar with
如果您已经对以下内容有所了解
the software you should be able to get a
您应该能够获得一个
sense of what I'm doing as I go through
在我经历的过程中感觉到我在做什么
these steps so I'm going to come over
这些步骤，所以我要过来
here into new document and get started
此处为新文档并开始使用
I'm going to draw a rectangle to start
我要画一个长方形开始
off and let me grab my selection tool
走了，让我拿起我的选择工具
I'm going to make this rectangle I
我要把这个长方形做成我
believe I used 400 by
我相信我用了400
250 and let me zoom in on this let me go
250，让我放大这个让我走
back to my rectangle tool I'm going to
回到我的矩形工具，我要
make these Corners a little
把这些角落弄得有点小
rounded there we go and now I'm going to
四舍五入我们走了，现在我要
put some circles in the corners to uh
在角落里画几个圆圈来呃
serve as screws the screws in the
作为螺丝将螺丝固定在
corners of the uh cassette tape so I'll
盒式磁带的角落，所以我会
put that right there and I'll make a few
把它放在那里，我会做几个
copies of this I'm going to press
我要把这个的复印件印出来
controll D or command D to duplicate it
控制D或命令D复制它
move this over
把这个搬过去
here make another duplicate of these
在这里再复制一份这些
bring these down here
把这些拿下来
and I'm going to group these together
我要把这些组合在一起
and I'm going to Center this up on the
我将把这一点集中在
document here so let me open this up and
文件在这里，让我打开它，
Center it so now I have the four screws
把它居中，这样我就有了四颗螺丝
centered in the uh corners of the
居中的，呃，角落里
cassette tape as you can see here that's
就像你在这里看到的盒式磁带
uh this part of the design so let me
呃，设计的这一部分，所以让我
come back in here and next I'm going to
回到这里，下一步我要
create the bottom part this uh this
创造底部这个这个
little bottom part of the design right
小底部的设计是正确的
here so I'm going to grab my rectangle
在这里，我要抓起我的矩形
tool again and I'm going to click and
工具，我要点击并
drag to draw a
拖动可绘制一个
rectangle and I'm going to make the
矩形和我要做的
corners of this one Shar for now I'm
这一个的角落现在我是共享的
going to go back and make those Corners
我要回去，走完那些弯道
rounded later on but I first want to
后来四舍五入，但我首先想
change the I want to distort the shape
更改我想要扭曲形状
of
的
this so I'll convert this to a
所以我会把它转换成一个
path grab my nodes tool and I want to
路径抓取我的节点工具，我想
grab these two nodes right here and let
抓住这里的这两个节点，让
me scale those down I don't know why
我不知道为什么要把它们缩小
that just layered beneath the other
就在另一层下面
object but I'll have to raise that up
反对，但我必须提出这个问题
again let me move that
再说一遍，让我移动一下。
up okay that looks good right there I
向上，好的，看起来很好，我
want to round these Corners a little bit
想绕过这些角落一点吗？
so I'm going to come over here and
所以我要到这里来，
choose the uh this handy new feature the
选择呃这个方便的新功能
corner is live path effect I'm going to
转角是活动路径效果，我要
select all of the
选择所有
nodes and I'm going to scale let me turn
节点和我要扩展让我转向
off the scaling handles and I'm going to
松开伸缩手柄，我要
bring this in like this just to make
把这个像这样拿进来只是为了
these
这些
rounded there we go and I just want to
四舍五入我们走了，我只想
make sure that this is centered there we
确保这个位于我们的中心位置
go and I'm going to put some
去吧，我要放一些
more I'm going to put these uh these
更多的是我要把这些呃这些
little round parts of the design in
设计中的小圆部分
there now so let me come back over here
好了，现在让我回到这里
and for that I'll just duplicate let me
为此，我只想重复一下，让我
ungroup these circles I'm just going to
解开这些圈子，我要去
duplicate these circles and use these
复制这些圆圈并使用这些
copies to make those uh to make those
复制来制作那些呃制作那些
parts of the design I'll scale that
部分设计，我将对其进行扩展
up duplicate that control D or command D
向上复制控件D或命令D
is the shortcut for duplicating very
是复制的快捷方式吗？
handy shortcut to
便捷的快捷方式
know move that over let me zoom out a
知道吗，把那个移过去，让我把它缩小
little bit to see how that looks in
稍微看看它是什么样子
proportion I guess that looks pretty
比例我想这看起来很不错
good maybe I'll make it a little
很好，也许我会做一点
smaller and I'm going to duplicate the
更小，我要复制
these and I will flip these horizontally
这些和我将水平翻转这些
and move these over here and now I want
把这些搬到这里来，现在我要
to Center this up on the uh bottom part
把这个放在呃底部的中心
of this design here so let me group that
所以让我把它归为一组
and I'll Center these
我会把这些放在中间
together let me move that down it looked
让我一起向下移动它看起来
better down there there we go now I can
在那里更好，我们现在可以走了
ungroup
解组
them okay so the next part of the design
他们没问题，所以设计的下一部分
I will make is I'll make this inner part
我要做的是我要做这个内心的部分
of the cassette tape or the label so let
盒式磁带或标签，所以让
me come back in here I'm going to grab
我回到这里，我要抓起
my rectangle tool and I'm going to make
我的矩形工具和我要做的
a rectangle in the uh on the inside of
在呃里面有一个长方形
the uh cassette tape there and let me
呃，盒式磁带在那里，让我
just make sure I have this centered up
只要确保我把这个放在中心就行了
on the other rectangle there we go and
在另一个矩形上，我们开始了
I'm going to change this a little bit
我要把这个稍微改一下
let me make this a little less tall
让我把这件事做得稍微低一点
vertically and I want to convert this to
垂直，我想把这个转换成
a path as well and now to make the
也是一条道路，现在要让
corners have this cut off effect we're
角落的影响被切断了，我们正在
going to use a path effect for that so
为此，我将使用路径效果
let me come back over here to my nodes
让我回到我的节点
tool and I want to enable the Corner's
工具和我想要启用角落的
live path effect again and I want to
Live Path Effect再次上演，我想
select both of these and now I can roll
这两个都选好了，现在我可以滚动了
them down like that now the corners are
他们就这样倒下了，现在角落里
rounded right now but that's okay we're
现在四舍五入，但没关系，我们是
going to go in and change that setting
我要进去改变这个设置
so I'm going to open up the path effects
因此，我将打开路径效应
menu path path
菜单路径路径
effects and now I should be able to
效果，现在我应该能够
change the corners to chamfer and now I
将拐角更改为倒角，现在我
have those squared Corners that I
我有那些方形的角落吗
preferred let me make those a little
首选，让我把那些做得有点
less let me scale those down a little
少一点，让我把那些缩小一点。
bit oh okay that looks good now we can
哦，好的，看起来不错，现在我们可以了
close out of that uh let me get out of
关闭那个，呃，让我离开
that and the next part I guess I will
还有下一部分，我想我会
make I I'll start working on the little
让我我会开始工作的小
spindles here in the center this is uh
主轴在中间，这是呃
probably the most elaborate part of this
可能这其中最精致的部分
whole thing so let's go get that
所以让我们去拿那个吧
started I'm going to grab my circles and
开始，我要抓起我的圈子
ellipses tool and I'm going to click and
省略号工具，我将点击并
drag to draw a
拖动可绘制一个
circle and let move this over I'm going
绕个圈，让它过去，我要走了
to duplicate this circle make this
要复制此圆，请执行以下操作
circle a little
稍微转一圈
smaller and I'm going to make these
再小一点，我要把这些
teeth that go on the inside of the uh
牙齿长在呃内侧
the spindle there so let me deselect
主轴在那里，所以让我取消选择
everything and to do this I'm going to
所有的一切，为了做到这一点，我要
use clones and this is going to make it
使用克隆人，这将使它
a lot easier to adjust things I'll show
调整要容易得多，我会展示给大家看
you what I mean here I'm going to click
你明白我的意思吗？我要点击
and drag to draw a rectangle it's going
然后拖动以绘制一个它将要移动的矩形
to represent one of the teeth of this uh
代表这颗牙齿中的一颗呢
of the spindle and I'm going to right
我要向右转
click this and go to instead of
点击此按钮并转到，而不是
duplicate I'm going to use clone and I'm
复制我将使用克隆，我将
going to take the Clone copy and I'm
我要拿到克隆拷贝，而我
going to bring it down
我要把它打倒
here and I just want to group both of
在这里，我只想把两位
these together make sure I have them
这些加在一起，确保我拥有它们
centered on the circle so let me come
以圆圈为中心，让我来吧
back over here to my aligned distribute
回到这里到我的对齐分发版
menu and now I'm going to clone these
菜单，现在我要克隆这些
again so I'm going to right click and go
再一次，我要右击并继续
to clone and I'm going to rotate this
来克隆，我要轮换这个
copy that many steps and then I'll clone
复制那么多步骤，然后我将克隆
that again so I'll right click that go
再来一次，我将右键单击该GO
to clone and I'll rotate it hold the
克隆它，我会旋转它，按住
control key and just rotate it around
Ctrl键，只需旋转它
like that there we go now the reason I
就像这样，我们现在去，原因是我
did that is because if I want to change
那是因为如果我想改变
the width of these teeth sometimes
有时这些牙齿的宽度
you'll make it too big or too small
你会把它做得太大或太小
without realizing it uh you'll have to
在没有意识到的情况下，呃，你不得不
go back and undo all of it when you use
返回并在使用时将其全部撤消
clones though you can just adjust one of
不过，克隆人只需调整其中一个
them and it adjusts all of them so I'm
它会调整所有的参数，所以我
going to hold my shift key and scale
按住我的Shift键和刻度盘
this part in like that and it's going to
这一部分像那样，它将会
change the size of all the other teeth
更改所有其他牙齿的大小
like that so let me move that out a
像这样，所以让我把它移到外面
little bit it looks better in a larger
大一点的看起来更好一点
size let me zoom out a little bit it's
尺码，让我放大一点，它是
hard to really perfectly visualize how
很难真正完美地想象出
it's going to look until you unify it
它会一直看，直到你把它统一起来
with the other
与另一只
shape let me try that one more
造型，让我再试一次。
time okay I think I'll leave that as it
时间没问题，我想我还是不说了。
is I'm going to select all of these now
我现在要选择所有这些
I have all of them selected and I'm
我把它们都选好了，我是
going to unlink the Clones so I'll go to
我要取消克隆的链接，因此我将转到
edit and I will choose clone and I will
编辑，我将选择克隆，我将
select unlink clone and now I can
选择取消链接克隆，现在我可以
ungroup them we'll go to object ungroup
将它们解组，我们将转到对象解组
and unify them all together path Union
并将它们统一在一起路径联盟
and then subtract it from that smaller
然后从那个小的减去它
Circle so I'll hold shift and click on
圈住Shift键并点击
that Circle and go to path difference
那圈和去的路径差
and now we have the teeth of the uh of
现在我们有了呃的牙齿
that wheel there let me scale that up a
那里的那个轮子让我把它放大
little
一点儿
bit and I'll take this part and scale
比特，我会把这一部分和规模
this
这
down and now I'm going to create the uh
向下，现在我要创建
the tape going around the uh the wheel
磁带绕着呃方向盘转
here so let me Zoom back out let me come
在这里，让我缩小，让我来
back in here and I'll take this larger
回到这里，我要这个大一点的
Circle I'm going to remove the fill and
圆圈我要去掉填充物
I'm going to make a duplicate of this
我要把这个复制一份
I'm going to press command D and then
我要按下命令D，然后
hold control and shift and scale this up
按住Ctrl和Shift并向上扩展
about that much and I'm going to take
差不多那么多，我要把它
both of these circles now and I'm going
现在这两个圈子我都要走了
to combine them together so I'll go to
将它们组合在一起，所以我将转到
path and I will choose combine and now
路径和我将选择合并，现在
I'm going to apply the interp
我要申请实习生
interpolate path effects so I'm going to
插入路径效果，这样我就可以
come over here to my path effects menu
到这里来我的路径效果菜单
and I'm looking for
我要找的是
interpolate uh interpolate interpolate
插话，嗯，插话插话
sub paths not points the one they use
子路径不指向它们使用的路径
here is sub paths and now I can increase
下面是子路径，现在我可以增加
or
或
decrease the uh number of paths between
减少UH之间的路径数
those circles I think this looks good
那些圆圈，我觉得这个看起来不错
with seven for now but I'm going to go
现在有七个人，但我要走了
back and change that later as I adjust
返回并在稍后我调整时更改它
things so for now that looks good I'll
所以现在看起来很好，我会
leave it at
让它保持在
seven and next I will I'm going to make
七个，下一个我要做的是
a duplicate copy of this and move this
复制一份这个并移动这个
over here so we have two of these now so
在这里，我们现在有两个这样的
I'm going to select all of these let me
我要选择所有这些让我
group it together let me duplicate this
把它组合在一起，让我复制这个
and just move this one over like
把这个移过去，就像这样
that and then I'll group these together
然后我会把这些组合在一起
and then Center them on this uh larger
然后把它们放在这个，呃，更大的
rectangle and that looks pretty
长方形的，看起来很漂亮
good okay let me ungroup those
好的，好的，让我来解开那些
now and now I'm going to trim off the
现在，我要修剪一下
edges I'm going create I'm going to
我要创造的边缘，我要
create the inner part like the window I
创建内部部分，就像窗户I
guess you can call it of this cassette
我想你可以把它叫做卡带。
tape and I'm going to trim off all of
胶带和我要修剪掉所有的
the other excess areas so let me come
其他多余的区域，让我来吧
back in here and to do that I'm going to
回到这里，为了做到这一点，我要
turn on my snapping and I'm going to
打开我的抓拍，我要
draw a
绘制一幅
rectangle I'll start the
矩形，我将开始
rectangle up here and I'll end it down
长方形在这里，我会结束它
here like that and I'm going to grab my
就像这样，我要拿起我的
selection tool now and I'm going to snap
现在选择工具，我要抓拍
it to the right Edge and then snap it to
将其放到右边缘，然后将其捕捉到
the left Edge basically I'm creating a
左边缘基本上我是在创建一个
rounded rectangle that goes around the
圆角矩形围绕
two wheels of the cassette tape so I'm
两个轮子的盒式磁带所以我
going to grab my rectangle tool now and
现在我要拿起我的矩形工具
round the
绕着
corners there we go that's the effect
转角，我们走，这就是效果
I'm going for and what I'll do next is
我要做的是，接下来我要做的是
I'm going to convert this to a path
我将把它转换成一条路径
we'll get to path object to
我们将获得路径对象以
path grab my selection tool and I'm
路径抓起我的选择工具，然后我
going to duplicate this and now I want
我要复制这个，现在我想
to select all of the wheels I'm going to
要选择我要选择的所有轮子
select the uh I'm going to select this
选择，呃，我要选择这个
wheel right here and I'm going to hold
方向盘就在这里，我要拿着
shift and select this wheel right here
按住Shift键并选择此处的滚轮
and I want to group them all together by
我想把它们全部归类到一起
pressing command G or contr G and I want
按COMMAND G或CONTR G，我想
to take this duplicate copy and then
拿着这份复制品，然后
select the grouped wheels and go to
选择分组的控制盘，然后转到
object clip set clip so now it is a
对象剪辑设置剪辑，因此现在它是一个
clipped object and what I could do now
剪裁的对象以及我现在可以做的事情
is I can take this rectangle and
我可以把这个长方形
duplicate that we'll go to duplicate and
复制，我们将去复制和复制
I will apply an offset to that so I will
我将对其应用补偿，因此我将
go to path and
转到PATH并
choose Dynamic
选择动态
offset let me go to my nodes tool I'm
偏移量让我转到我的节点工具
going to take this node and bring that
我要用这个节点，把那个
out let me turn off my snapping for now
出去，让我暂时关掉我的抓拍
and I think that looks pretty good as it
我认为这看起来很好
is I think I'll will leave it like that
我想我会就这么走了
now I want to create some asymmetry
现在我想创造一些不对称
between these two wheels here if you
在这两个轮子之间，如果你
notice in my original design there's
请注意，在我最初的设计中，有
more tape on this wheel than there is on
这个轮子上的胶带比上面的多
this wheel so that's the effect I want
这个轮子，这就是我想要的效果
to uh I want to create to do that I'm
为了，呃，我想创造这样做，我是
going to uh and this is where path
去，呃，这就是小路
effects really come in handy because
效果真的派上用场，因为
this is still editable as a path effect
此选项仍可作为路径效果进行编辑
so if I go to my nodes tool I can still
因此，如果我转到节点工具，我仍然可以
select this and I'm going to select
选择这个，我就会选择
these nodes I'm going to hold shift and
我将按住Shift键和这些节点
click on them and I'll turn on my
点击它们，我将打开我的
transformation handles and now I can
变形手柄，现在我可以
scale this up like that and all those
像这样扩大规模，所有这些
other circles in there scale with it the
那里的其他圆圈也随着它的变化而变化
problem is that there are a little more
问题是，有更多的
SPAC out so I'm going to go back into my
空格出来，所以我要回到我的
uh path effects menu and add some more
UH路径效果菜单，并添加更多内容
sub paths in
中的子路径
there and I'll do the opposite over here
在那里，我会在这里做相反的事情
I'll maybe shrink this one down a little
我可能会把这件缩小一点。
bit let me move this
比特，让我把这个搬开
over and let me select these
过来，让我来选择这些
nodes and I'll scale these ones
节点，我将对这些节点进行缩放
down and now I will remove some of those
向下，现在我将移除一些
sub paths in there to make it look
子路径在那里，让它看起来
evenly spaced out with the other ones so
与其他的间隔均匀，所以
that looks a lot better I think let me
那看起来好多了，我想让我
turn off the uh transformation
关闭这个转换
handles and that looks a lot better we
手柄，看起来好多了，我们
have some asymmetry there now between
现在两者之间有一些不对称
those two uh objects now I just want to
那两个物体，现在我只想
size this up so it fits the cassette
把这个大小调整一下，这样才能适合盒式磁带
tape overall and uh and it's nicely
整个录像带，呃，它很好
aligned um you know what before I do
对齐了，嗯，你知道在我之前
that let's trim off all of this other
让我们把其他的都剪掉
excess stuff because if I go to my nodes
多余的东西因为如果我去我的节点
tool you can see if I hover my cursor
如果我将光标悬停，您可以看到
these other lines still exist with
这些其他的线仍然存在于
within the clip you just don't see them
在这段视频中，你根本看不到它们
because they're hidden behind the
因为他们隐藏在
clipping mask that we created I want to
我们创建的剪贴蒙版，我想
finalize these and make these um like
最后完成这些，并使这些嗯像
plain Vector paths so to do that I'm
普通向量路径，为此，我是
going to select this all and I'm going
我要选择这一切，我要去
to come over here into the shape Builder
进入形状构建器的步骤
tool and now I'm just going to build the
工具，现在我将构建
shape that I want out of this so I'm
塑造我想要的样子，所以我
going to click on this part to add that
我要点击此部件以添加
and everything that I make blue is going
我做的每一件事都是蓝色的
to be what gets kept and everything
成为被保留的东西和一切
that's not blue will be deleted so I'm
不是蓝色的会被删除，所以我
going to combine all of this
我将把这一切结合起来
together
在一起
and I'm making separate shapes out of
我正在制作不同的形状
each of these because I want everything
每一个都是因为我想要一切
in here to be its own shape so I can add
在这里是它自己的形状，所以我可以添加
color to it which you will see in just a
为它添加颜色，您将在
few minutes so that right there is what
几分钟，所以就在那里
I'm going for I want everything divided
我要去，我要把所有的东西都分了
into its own shape and if I go back to
变成它自己的形状，如果我回到
my selection tool now it is everything
我的选择工具现在它就是一切
uh it's designed just how I want it so I
呃，它的设计正是我想要的，所以我
have these individual shapes here that I
在这里有这些单独的形状，我
can edit and work with however I need so
我可以编辑和工作，但我需要这样
now that that's done let me select
现在已经完成了，让我选择
everything here and group it together
并将这里的所有内容组合在一起
and I want to center it up over this
我想把它集中在这个上面
rectangle so let me come back into my
所以让我回到我的
alignment tab and I may have to make
对齐标签和我可能不得不制作
this one a little bigger relative to the
相对于这个，这个有点大
relative to the uh the tape because
相对于录像带来说，因为
normally the wheel goes out almost past
正常情况下，轮子几乎会经过
the corner of this uh part of the tape
录像带的这个呃部分的一角
right here so I got to make mine oops
就在这里，所以我要做我的
let me undo that I got to make mine a
让我来挽回这一切，我要让我的
little bigger uh maybe not bigger but
有点大，呃，可能不大，但
longer so let me ungroup everything I'm
更长的时间，让我解开我的一切
going to grab my nodes tool and I'm
去拿我的节点工具，然后我
going to select these nodes over here
在这里选择这些节点
and I'll just move these over like
我会把这些搬过来，就像
that and now we're elongating it without
现在我们把它拉长到没有
having to um scale it so let me group it
必须对其进行呃缩放，所以让我对其进行分组
together now and let me try centering it
现在放在一起，让我试着居中
again see if it looks any better and
再看看它看起来是不是更好
that's more along the lines of what I'm
这更像是我所说的
going for you know what I think
你知道我怎么想的吗？
something got taken off center here let
这里有些东西偏离了中心，让
me redo that this is one of the
我再说一遍，这是
downsides of working with a trackpad if
在以下情况下使用触摸板的缺点
I'm working with the mouse I don't have
我在用我没有的鼠标工作
that problem so now let's uh let's make
那个问题，所以现在让我们，呃，让我们
these little lines right here this this
这些小线条就在这里这是这
is like a blank label where you can
就像一张空白标签，你可以
write in your own label on the cassette
在盒式磁带上写上你自己的标签
tape I'm going to grab the pen tool to
我要把钢笔工具拿到胶带上
make
制作
those hold control so we get a straight
他们掌握着控制权，所以我们得到了直通
line press enter to close the path and
LINE按Enter键关闭路径并
I'm going to make this the same size as
我要把这件衣服做得和
The Strokes on the other shapes which is
其他形状上的笔触
three so I'll come back over here stroke
三个，所以我会回到这里，击球
style tab make this three pixels I want
Style标签设置为我想要的三个像素
this to have rounded
这要有四舍五入
caps and I'll make a duplicate of this
帽子和我会把这个复制一份
and bring this down here so I'm going to
把这个拿到这里来，所以我要
hold the control
控制住手柄
key that looks good maybe I'll make this
看起来不错的钥匙，也许我会做这个
a little
一点
bigger and I'm just going to size this
更大的，我要把它的大小
up and adjust it until it looks
向上调整，直到它看起来
right okay there we go so I'm going for
好的，好的，我们走吧，所以我要
a nice balanced look here where
一个很好的平衡的外观在这里
everything is spaced up spaced out
所有的东西都是错开的
nicely I'm going to ungroup that now and
很好，我现在要把它解开
the cassette tape part of the design is
设计的盒式磁带部分是
finished now I want to create this um
完成了，现在我想创建这个
this rainbow ribbon background here that
这里的彩虹带背景
I put behind the cassette tape so let me
我把录音带放在后面，所以让我
come back over here for this I want to
回来这里拿这个我想
make sure I have my snapping enabled and
确保我启用了捕捉功能，并且
I'm going to grab my rectangle tool and
我要拿起我的矩形工具
I'm going to draw a elongated
我要画一张拉长的
rectangle and I'm going to make the
矩形和我要做的
corner Sharp and I want to make cop I
角落夏普和我想让警察一号
want to make five copies of this so I'm
我想复印五份，所以我
going to press control D to make a copy
按下Ctrl D复制一份
I'll snap this copy over here to the
我会把这份拷贝放在这里
left end or to the right end and I'll
左端或右端，我将
just repeat this until I have five
重复这个，直到我有五个
copies there we go let me select all of
副本在那里我们去让我选择所有
those convert them to a
它们会将它们转换为
path path object to path and now I'm
路径路径对象到路径，现在我是
going to do I'm going to duplicate these
我要把这些复制一遍
and I'm going to put these down here and
我要把这些放在这里
snap these to the bottom and this time
把这些扣到底部，这次
I'm going to go with combin so I'll go
我要和康宾一起去，所以我要去
with uh path and and I will choose
有了这个路径，我会选择
combine and I'm going to move this
合在一起，我要把这个
up and now I want to use the perspective
现在我想用透视图
path effect to make this uh wider so I'm
路径效应，让它变得更宽，所以我
going to come back over here to my path
会回到我的道路上来
effects and I'm looking for
效果，我正在寻找
perspective there we go grab my nodes
透视图在那里，我们去抓住我的节点
tool I want to lock this in the uh or
工具我想把这个锁在呃或者
mirror it in the vertical axis and now I
在垂直轴上镜像它，现在我
can just scale that out like
可以像这样向外扩展
that that looks pretty good now I'm
这看起来很不错，现在我
going to convert that to a path as well
也要将其转换为路径
we go to path object to path grab my S
我们去路客体去路夺我的S
ction tool and I want to break this
Ction Tool和我想打破这一点
apart so I'll go to path and I will
分开，所以我会去小路，我会
choose break apart and now these should
选择拆分，现在这些应该
already be broken apart yeah I need
已经支离破碎了是的我需要
these to be individual objects so what
这些都是单独的物体，那又怎么样
I'm going to do is I'm going to start
我要做的是我要开始
unifying these objects together I'm
把这些东西统一在一起，我是
going to hold my option key or ALT key
按住Option键或Alt键
and just draw a line between those two
在这两者之间划一条线
objects unify them together by going to
对象通过转到
path Union or the keyboard shortcut is
路径并集或键盘快捷键是
control shift and the plus key so I'm
Ctrl Shift和加号键，所以我
just going to use that for the rest of
我只想在接下来的时间里用它
these we're going to repeat this process
我们将重复这个过程
I'm going select those unify those
我要选择那些统一那些
together
在一起
do the same thing over here oops let me
在这里做同样的事情，哦，让我
un deselect
取消选择
that control shift plus
控制换档加
deselect select these ones and there you
取消选择这些选项，您就可以
go one more to
再往前走一步
go okay so that's what we're going for
去吧，好的，这就是我们要去的
now and to make these rounded what I
现在，为了让这些变得圆润起来，我
will do is I want to select all of them
我要做的就是我想把它们全部选出来
first so I'm going to hold shift and
首先，我要按住Shift，然后
click on each of
点击每一项
these
这些
and I want to combine these together so
我想把这些结合在一起，所以
I'll go to path and I will choose
我会去PATH，我会选择
combine let me move move this out of the
组合，让我移动，把这个移出
way of the cassette tape I'm going to
我要去看录音带的方式
turn off the snapping now and I'm going
现在关掉快门，我要走了
to go back to the nodes tool and I'm
返回到节点工具，然后我
going to turn on the corner live path
要在拐角的活动小路上转弯
effect for this and I'm going to select
效果，我将选择
these nodes right here let me try that
这里的这些节点让我试一试
again there we go and I'm just going to
我们又来了，我要去
round this like that so we get a nice
像这样绕来绕去，这样我们就能得到一个很好的
rounded effect
舍入效果
there
那里
okay that looks good I'll leave that as
好的，看起来不错，我就不说了。
it is and now I'm going to go into my
是的，现在我要走进我的
shape Builder tool and I'm just going to
Shape Builder Tool和我正准备
click on each of these one by one to
逐一单击其中的每一项以
make sure that they are all separate
确保它们都是分开的
shapes and that they no longer have the
形状，并且它们不再具有
path effect applied they're just plain
应用了路径效应，它们很简单
Vector pads and there you go now we're
向量板，你现在就可以了
finished so let me go back over here now
完成了，现在让我回到这里
and I could take this and move this over
我可以拿着这个，把这个移到
here you know what let me leave this
在这里，你知道是什么让我留下这个
here I'm going to take the cassette tape
现在我要把盒式磁带
group it together and place it over on
将它组合在一起，并将其放在
top of uh this backdrop here I want to
在这个背景之上，我想要
raise this up so it's layered above
把这个抬起来，这样它就在上面分层了
it and I'm going to Center both of
它和我都将成为
these and the final step is to just add
最后一步就是添加
some color as you can see that I've done
如你所见，我做了一些颜色
over here in my original design so let
在我的原创设计中，所以让
me come back in here I'm going to start
我回来了，我要开始了
coloring this thing in so I'll start
给这个东西涂上颜色，这样我就开始
with these stripes down here let me
有了这些条纹，让我
ungroup these or break them apart rather
将它们解开，或者将它们分开
object path break
对象路径分隔符
apart and for the colors it was just red
除了颜色，它只是红色的
orange yellow green and blue so I'll add
橙色、黄色、绿色和蓝色，所以我要加上
some variation of those Shades let me
这些色调的一些变化让我
start with this
从这个开始
one and now I'm going to start adding
一个，现在我要开始添加
some color to the cassette tape so let
给盒式磁带涂上一些颜色，这样就可以
me ungroup that
我把它拆开
now and I want to change the color I'm
现在我想改变我的颜色
going to use this object right here as a
我将在这里将此对象用作
starting point I'll make that one white
起始点，我会把它改成白色的
and I'll make this one white as well and
我会把这个也改成白色的
the smaller shape inside of it I'm going
里面的较小的形状我要去
to hold my ALT key to select that
按住Alt键以选择该选项
smaller shape and I'm going to make this
更小的形状，我要把这个
a dark shade of gray about as dark as it
一种深灰色，和它一样暗
can get without it Contra without it
没有它我也能过得很好
losing its contrast with the black
失去了与黑色的对比
stroke so I'm going to go with a really
中风，所以我要用一个真正的
dark shade let me go over here to my
黑暗的阴影让我从这里走到我的
fill and stroke menu and adjust this
填充和描边菜单并调整此选项
manually make it a little darker that
手动使它变得更暗一点
looks pretty good and I'm going to use
看起来很不错，我要用
this shade for a lot of other things so
这个色调可以用来做很多其他的事情
I'm going to select this one over here
我要选这里的这个
use the same color with my dropper tool
使用与我的滴管工具相同的颜色
and I will select this shape in
我将在中选择此形状
here let me try that again there we go I
这里，让我再试一次，我们开始吧
want to make that the same color and I
我想把它做成和我一样的颜色
want to make all of these wheels that
想要制造所有这些轮子，
same color or that same shade of gray
相同的颜色或相同的灰色
rather there we go and I could take this
宁可我们去那里，我可以带着这个
rectangle I'm going to make this a
矩形，我要把它变成一个
darker shade of gray I'll make this a
更深的灰色，我会把它变成
lighter shade of
浅色调的
gray and I'll make this one over here a
格雷和我要把这里的这个做成一个
much lighter shade of gray it's going to
它将会变成更浅的灰色
be gray but it's going to be much
头发是灰色的，但它将会很多
lighter and now I'm going to take the uh
打火机，现在我要把呃
well I'm going to take this shape right
好的，我要把这个形状做对
here I'll start here and I will make
在这里我会从这里开始，我会
this the same shade of gray that this
这是和这一样的灰色
cassette tape is and now I can take the
盒式磁带是的，现在我可以把
tape inside of here or the rolls of uh
里面的胶带或者卷成卷的
tape and I'm going to select all of
磁带，我将选择所有
those and make them this shade maybe
然后把它们做成这个色调
I'll make these a little bit
我会把这些做一点
darker and then I'll do the same thing
更暗，然后我会做同样的事情
over here with these ones I'll select
在这里，我会选择这些
these ones as
这些是作为
well and I'm not quite satisfied with
嗯，我并不是很满意
the contrast between these darker Shades
这些较深色调之间的对比
of Gray so let me make those a little
所以让我把这些做一点
darker I'm going to select that and I
更黑暗，我要选择那个，然后我
want to apply this to all of the other
我想要将这一点应用于所有其他
objects that have that color so I'll go
有这种颜色的物品，所以我会去
to edit select same and I'll choose fill
要编辑，请选择Same，我将选择Fill
color and now that I have those all
颜色，现在我有了所有这些
selected I can change the shade and
选中后，我可以更改阴影和
darken it as
把它调暗为
needed okay that looks good
需要，好的，看起来不错
enough all right so I guess one last
够了，好吧，我想最后一次
step would be to add a background as
步骤是将背景添加为
I've done here let me just go back in
我已经做完了，让我回去吧
here I'm going to turn on snapping to do
在这里，我将打开捕捉以执行以下操作
this makes it a lot easier I'll snap to
这让我在接下来的时间里
this corner and then I'll snap to this
在这个角落，然后我会抓住这个
corner up here and now I can just grab
在这里的角落里，现在我可以抓住
my selection tool and scale this out as
我的选择工具，并将其扩展为
needed again using the snapping controls
需要再次使用捕捉控件
let me send this to the
让我把这个寄给
bottom let me make this a shade of
最后，让我把这件事说得有点像
yellow I'll use this as a starting point
黄色，我将以此为起点。
but I want it to be
但我想让它成为
lighter and there you go that should do
轻一点，你就可以这样做了
it for this tutorial that's how you can
对于本教程，这就是您可以
use some of the more advanced uh node
使用一些更高级的呃节点
editing features in in incap to create
在INCAP中编辑要素以创建
something like this cassette tape design
类似于这种盒式磁带的设计
if you found this lesson useful then
如果你觉得这一课很有用，那么
consider checking out my inkscape master
考虑一下我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where I go over all of the tools
我浏览了所有工具的视频
and features in inkscape and I explain
和Inkscape中的功能，我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并演示它们如何
work kind of like how I did in this
就像我在这件事上做的那样
video we even have a private Community
视频我们甚至有一个私人社区
where you can ask questions and get help
在这里您可以提出问题并获得帮助
from me anytime you want and best of all
在你想要的任何时候从我这里，最好的是
there's no monthly membership fees you
你不需要缴纳月费
just pay $17 one time and you're in for
只需一次性支付17美元，你就会面临
Life I'll have some information about
我会有一些关于生活的信息
that down if you want to check that out
如果你想看看的话就把它放下
as always thanks for
一如既往地感谢
[Music]
[音乐]
watching
观看